http://www.magsr.org/content/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Main menu
HomeAdoption CenterMAGSR MalesMAGSR Femalesnon-MAGSR/Shelter DogsAdopted DogsSuccess StoriesSad newsAdoption ApplicationAbout GSD'sGSD Adoption MythsAdopting Senior DogsDaisy's StorySamson's StoryChoosing a TrainerTrainersCrate TrainingCanine Health CareGSD Health IssuesIs a GSD Right for You?Our HeroesWhy Adopt an Adult Dog?After the AdoptionGSD LinksHelp the DogsWays You Can HelpDonationsSponsor a DogThe MAGSR Medical FundThe MAGSR Senior FundVolunteer ApplicationFoster ApplicationAdoption ApplicationMAGSR MerchandiseAffiliate ShoppingOur Supporters2020 Adopters Reunion SponsorsMAGSR Events2020 Fall Volunteer Festival20th Anniversary Reunion Pics2018 Adopters Reunion PicsAbout UsAbout Mid-Atlantic German Shepherd RescueAbout MAGSR - FAQAdoption InformationOnce You Have A DogSurrenderingVolunteering & HelpingPrivacy PolicyContact MAGSRShopMAGSR LinksTracking CollarsPet Medical LinksGSD Rescue USAOther Breed Local RescuesArea SheltersPet Friendly HousingLost & FoundRescue PoemsPetitions & AlertsKennels and DaycareDownloads
This Website is owned and operated by the Mid-Atlantic German Shepherd Rescue. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time.
The Mid-Atlantic German Shepherd Rescue (MAGSR) maintains this website. Web sites run on web servers. Web servers talk to web browsers. Web browsers, when talking to web servers, automatically share certain bits of non-personal information. This information may include network address , browser type , and so on. That stuff gets recorded in the web server's log.  We look at our logs sometimes to see what pages are linking to our site or how many people clicked on a certain page.
MAGSR respects the privacy of its online visitors; and on our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. For example, when you send feedback to MAGSR, you may be asked for your name and e-mail address. This is so we can address you as a human being in our correspondence. MAGSR will use this information to respond to your request. There are times, however, when your e-mail is forwarded within our organization to other volunteers who are better able to assist you. MAGSR may also forward requests for assistance to other appropriate institutions for response (outside our area of expertise). Except for the foregoing example, and as required by law, we will never share, sell, lend, shout loudly in a crowded theater, or otherwise distribute your personal information without your consent.  If you click the "send" box on our comment forms, you are giving us permission to use your comment -- just your comment -- in promotional material for the site.
This web site has links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. We do not control those sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for their availability, content, or delivery of services.  If you have questions about this site, its collection of information, and its online privacy policy, please contact us. Once again, please understand that we do not collect personal information unless it is provided voluntarily and knowingly. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children without parent's permission. You may remove any personal information from our database to discontinue communications or service by contacting us. We use appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and the privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our site and periodically update measures with new technologies. When appropriate, MAGSR uses encryption technologies, user authentication systems, and access control mechanisms.  This web site contains links to other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, our contact information can be found on our contact us page at:  Contact us
Thank you for visiting our site. Please contact us should you have any questions about the operation of the site.
Follow MAGSR on:
Shop MAGSR
Support MAGSR by promoting MAGSR
Pet Safety Tips
Pet Safety Tips
Helpful tips to keep your pets safe, from SimpliSafe.
Walk for A Dog App
Support MAGSR simply by walking your dog, child or just by walking by yourself. Get the free app for "Walk for a Dog" at WoofTrax.com. Just install the app, enroll in the program for free, select Mid-Atlantic German Shepherd Rescue as your chosen organization and start walking!!! The Walk for a Dog program will donate to MAGSR every time you walk! Get walking to support the pups!    #WalkforaDog
Adopters' Update
MAGSR Moms and Dads, let's keep in touch. Keep your contact info up to date, let us know about any changes HERE
